University Elementary School. Library. Administrative files. 1920-1991.
UCLA Library Special Collections
University Elementary School. Library. Administrative files.
1920-1991
University Archives Record Series 702
UCLA Library Special Collections
0.8 linear ft. (2 boxes)
Record Series 702 contains the administrative files of the UCLA University Elementary School Library. Files include correspondence, reports, budgets, and other administrative materials.
University of California, Los Angeles. University Elementary School.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 702 contains the administrative files of the UCLA University Elementary School Library. Files include correspondence, reports, budgets, and other administrative materials.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4475143
- Reports: Annual & Semi-Annual., 1947-1969. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reports: Annual & Semi-Annual., 1971-1991. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Book Budget to 1965., 1952-1967. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Corinne Seeds Memorial Funds., 1969-1970. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - External., 1962-1967. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Internal., 1957-1968. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Personal. RESTRICTED., 1961-1967. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Statistical Report Summary Circulation by User Category., 1978. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Capital Improvements., 1945-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Gifts., 1949-1965. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Reports: Quarterly., 1965-1970. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Reports: Monthly., 1944-1965. (Box 2, Folder 2)